声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：66 亚历9大 wolfRay paradise 螃蟹 小帝
校对：许愿 时间轴：YY吕伟 carrera.liu
========== 字幕总监制：何何 思思  ==========
如果你这样做  我们就放了你和Walt
And if you do, we'll let you and walt go free.
我会做的  给我枪
I'll do it. Give me the gun.
我会杀了他的
I'll kill him.
Michael?
你履行了你的承诺
You lived up to your word.
我们也说话算数
We live up to our word, too.
你坐这条船
You're gonna take this boat
然后沿着罗盘指向3-2-5位置
And follow a compass bearing of 3-2-5,
如果你能精确的那么做
And if you do that exactly,
你和你儿子就会得救
You and your son will find rescue.
你们这些人到底是谁?
Who are you people?
我们是好人  Michael
We're the good guys, Michael.
-Walt!  -Dad!
-Walt!  -dad!
快过来  快过来
Come here! come here!
谢谢你们大家的耐心等待
Thank you all for your patience.
我知道我已经花了好几天时间去...
I know it's taken me a few days to...
确定我们下一步行动  不过我还不想有任何行动
Figure out our next move, but I don't want to do anything
除非我知道更多我们的情况
until I knew more about our situation.
你们应该也要和我一样知道一切
You deserve to know everything that I do,
所以...我要告诉你们一切
So... no more secrets.
你们都知道
As you all know,
Miles还有他的三个人
Miles here and three of his people
大概一星期前来到岛上
Came to the island about a week ago.
所以我把他从船上绑来
So I brought him up from the boathouse
跟我们分享
To share with us
到底他们为什么来这儿
Exactly why they're here.
我们是为他而来的
We're here for him.
我们大概  几万年前就知道这个了
Um, we kind of, like, knew that forever ago.
那么好了
Well, all right then.
问题解决了  我们什么时候把他交出去?
Problem solved.How soon do we turn him over?
我们不能
we can't turn him over.
-到底为什么不能?  -因为一旦他们抓到了我
-And why the hell not?  -Because once they have me,
他们的指令就是杀掉岛上的其他所有人
Their orders are to kill everyone else on the island.
等等  那么...他现在是我们中一员了?
Wait. so...what, he's one of us now?
你是要  你是要保护他?
You're--you're gonna protect him?
他可曾经想杀了你的啊  John
He tried to kill you, john.
对  他也不会告诉我们他在船上的间谍是谁
Yeah. He won't even tell us who his spy on the boat is.
是Michael
It's michael.
什么?
What?
我在货船上的间谍是Michael
My spy on the freighter is Michael.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你说的是冷血地杀了两个女人
You mean the same guy that killed two women in cold blood
放了那个混蛋
To set this little bastard free?
然后把我们都出卖了才离开岛上的
And then sold all of us out so he could get off the island
-那个Michael?  -是的  James
-That michael?  -Yes, james.
是那个Michael
That Michael.
逃亡的规则...
The rules of desertion...
仍然适用于每个人
Still apply to everyone.
没有我的话  谁也别想离开这条船
Nobody leaves this ship without my say-so!
我打这些人不是去吓你们
I'm not beating these men to scare you.
我打他们是为了救你们的命
I beat them to save your lives!
你还记得上次那两个
Do you remember what happened to the last two men
离开的人怎么了吗?
Who took off in is boat?
你还记得Minkowski怎么了吗?
You remember what happened to minkowski?
只要我们一修好引擎
As soon as we get the engines fixed,
我们就继续搜索
We're back in the hunt.
同时
In the meantime,
大家都不要轻举妄动
Everybody just hold on.
Johnson!
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
把这儿打扫干净
Clean this mess up.
先生
Sir.
你好  Michael
Hello, michael.
-伙计 现在不行  -就是现在
-Not now, man.  -Yes,right now.
你为什么在这船上?
Why are you on this boat?
我是来寻死的
I'm here to die.
遇见你真好  John
That was a nice meetin', John,
不过我想不会再有更多秘密了
But I thought there wasn't gonna be any more secrets.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我是说你们这些家伙要的
I'm talking about the 3 million bucks
300万美元
Your buddy here asked for.
Miles用他的忠诚换钱
Miles offered his loyalty in exchange for the money.
不过既然没看到岛上有银行
But as I haven't seen a bank on the island,
我觉得这个根本不值一提
I didn't think it worth mentioning.
有什么好笑的?
Somethin' funny?
Linus会找到办法拿到的
Linus will find a way to get it.
那他会怎么做?
And how will he do that?
他想存活下来
He wants to survive.
还有考虑到一星期前你拿着枪指着他的头
And considering a week ago you had a gun to his head,
而今晚他却在吃碎蛋糕
And tonight he's eating pound cake...
我得说这个家伙得到了他想要的
I'd say he's a guy who gets what he wants.
好的  谢谢
It's fine. Okay, thanks.
拜拜  大家
Bye, guys.
Alex?
我能和你说句话吗?
May I have a word with you?
我们已经听够了你这一晚上的唠叨了
I think we've heard enough from you for one night.
抱歉  你们还是要再多听一会
I'm sorry. You're just gonna have to listen to a little more.
好的  你要干嘛?
It's okay. What do you want?
这是去神殿的地图
This is a map to the temple.
那是个圣地
It's a sanctuary.
这可能是岛上最后的安全地带了
It may be the last safe place on this island.
我们怎么不知道这个?
How can we don't know about this?
如果我告诉大家  那个地方就不是圣地了  对吗?
Well, it wouldn't be a sanctuary if I told everyone, would it?
我们剩余的人已经都在那儿了
The rest of our people are already there.
如果你们现在出发  一天半就可以到那儿
If you leave now, you can get there in a day and a half.
如果那儿很安全  为什么我们不都去
If it's safe, why don't we all go--Hurley,
Hurley  Claire  婴儿?
Claire, the baby?
因为神殿 不是给他们的  Karl  只是给我们的
Because the temple's Not for them, Karl. It's only for us.
这些正在赶来的人  他们知道我是谁  Alex
These people that are coming-- they know who I am, Alex.
我们会杀了任何妨碍他们的人
They'll kill anybody that get in their way.
如果他们知道了你是谁  知道了你是我女儿
If they knew who you were, that you were my daughter,
他们就会利用你来抓我
They would use you to get to me.
我们没多少时间了
We don't have much time.
也许他是对的
Maybe he's right.
我同意 我们应该走
I agree. We should go.
这些人  你说他们很危险
These people-- you said they're dangerous.
比你更危险?
More dangerous than you?
是的
Yes.
不过你母亲会保护你的
But your mother will protect you.
好了  走吧
Okay, now go.
他在哪?
Where is he?
-你确定?  -是的
-You sure? -Yeah.
他在动力室
He's in the engine room.
我不知道  这个应该会有用的
I don'understand it. It should be working.
垫圈都被腐蚀了
Gaskets are all corroded.
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you?
船长派我们下来帮忙修理
The captain sent us down to help with the repairs
谢谢  我们能行
Oh, thanks. We're okay.
Jeff  你知道吗?
Hey, Jeff, man, you know what?
我们需要个压力阀  你介意去补给室
We need a pressure valve. you mind grabbing one
去一个来吗?  -不介意
-From the, uh, supply room?  -Not at all.
你不应该在这儿
You shouldn't be here.
-Sayid  你在做什么?  -你为什么在这?
-Oh, Sayid, what are you doing? -Why are you here?
-如果他们看到我和你说话  -那就快说
-If they see me talking to you-- -Then talk quickly.
-你根本不会明白的!  -我会完全明白的  Michael
You won't understand it! I'll understand perfectly, Michael.
你从头开始
You just start from the beginning
解释下你是怎么来到这船上的
And explain how you came to be on this boat.
对不起  Dawson先生  我本不想吵醒你
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to wake you, mr. dawson.
你是?
It's...
我怎么了?
What happened to me?
你出车祸了  你能活下来真是个奇迹
You were in a car accident. it's a miracle you're alive.
我伤得有多重？
How badly am I hurt?
你现在需要休息
Shh. you just need to rest now.
晚上很凉
It's a cold night.
我帮你加一床毯子
I brought you some extra blankets.
让我们开灯看看
Ugh. let's get some light in here.
我好像听到有人在叫
Now I thought I heard someone shout,
很明显不是他
and something tells me it wasn't him.
你还好吗
You okay?
你能活着真是运气太好了
You're lucky to be alive.
急救队在一个撞得变形的车里找到了你
E.m.t.s say they found you in a wrecked car
有张纸条别在你的胸前
There's a note pinnedo your chest.
你身上没有身份证
You didn't have any i.d. on you.
能告诉我你叫什么吗？
you Want to tell me your name?
好吧 看来你不想
Yeah, I didn't think so.
你需要我们通知Walt吗
You want me to call walt?
你说什么?
What?
粘在你胸前的纸条
The note pinned to your chest.
上写着Walt  要我们通知他吗
It was written to "walt." you want me to call him?
不
No.
那好吧
Okay, then.
嗨  妈
Hey, ma.
我能进去...坐坐吗
Can i... come in?
不能  你知道的
No. you know the answer to that.
-我想要看看他  -不行
I wanna see him. no.
-让我解释一下  -我不想让你跟那个孩子谈什么
Just let me talk-- I don't know what you said to that boy,
不管怎样  他不想见你
But whatever it was, he doesn't want to see you.
拜托了  妈  他是我的儿子  我有个那个权利
Please, ma. he's my son. I have a right
他以为你已经死了
He thought you were dead.
他们说你坐的飞机在大海中坠毁了
They said your plane crashed in the middle of the ocean,
但你又出现了  毫发无损
But you show up here fine and dandy,
只有你和Walt才知道怎么和别人说
Only I can't tell anybody but you or walt,
我不能叫你的真名
I can't call you by your real names.
他几乎不和我说话
He barely talks to me,
但他却在半夜被噩梦惊醒
But he does wake up screamin' in the middle of the night,
只有我对他说
And I'm the one who got to tell him
宝贝  没事的
It's gonna be okay.
你得给我解释清楚
So until you can explain to me
这两个月你去哪儿了?
Where you were for over two months
发生了什么事了?
And what happened...
你已经放弃了你的权利
You gave up your rights.
你能不能
Will you, uh...
告诉他  我爱他
Will you tell him I love him?
可以
Yeah.
有什么可以帮你的吗
What can I do for ya?
这个值多少钱
How much can I get for that?
为什么上面有中文
Why is there chinese writing all over it?
是韩文  一个韩国人给我的
It's korean,an-- the guy who gave it to me.
你看起来不会说韩语
You don't look like you speak korean.
-我给你300美元  -我不是要钱
I'll give you $300 for it. I'm not looking for money.
那你要什么
What are you looking for?
我要一把枪和一些子弹
I want a gun. I want a gun with bullets.
好吧  该结束了
Come on. let's just get this done.
帮我结束它吧
Help me just get this done.
打扰了  先生  你有时间吗
Excuse me, sir. you got the time?
不  没有
No, man. no.
好了  Michael
Come on, michael.
帮帮老朋友吧
How about for an old friend?
你来曼哈顿了啊?
Manhattan, huh?
我们让你离开了那个岛
We let you leave one island,
结果你又到了这个岛（曼哈顿）
you just go to another one.
你能不能放松点  我只是来...
Will you just relax? I just came here to
现在能像个成年人一样和我谈话了吗？
Now are u ready to talk like adults?
是的
Yeah.
够了
Enough!
开枪吧  开吧  开啊
Do it. go ahead, do it!
你想死  是吧
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
你怎么找到我的?
How do you find me?
Michael  是我们让你回家的
We are the ones who sent you home, michael.
你真的天真得以为我们会放过你？
Did you honestly think we weren't gonna keep tabs?
你到底想要什么?
What do you want?
你的帮忙
Your help.
我为什么要帮一个
Why would I help the son of a bitch
绑架了我儿子的杂种?
Who kidnapped my son?
Mike  我们毫发无损地把他还给你了
We gave him back to you in one piece, mike.
是你把他丢了
You're the one who lost him.
你告诉他了  是不是？
You told him, didn't you?
想想你自己对那些女人都做了什么
You couldn't carry the guilt
你自己承担不了那份内疚
Of what you did to those two women all by yourself,
所以你要一个10岁大的孩子帮你分担
So you shared it with a 10-year-old kid.
这是不是你要自杀的原因  Michael？
Is that why you wanna kill yourself, micel?
因为他是那样认为你的
Because that's the way he looks at you now?
-因为他知道你是个杀人犯  -滚！
Because he knows you're a murderer? go away!
我有些坏消息要告诉你  Amigo
I got some bad news for you, amigo.
你不能自杀  那个岛也不会让你这么干的
You can't kill yourself. the island won't let you!
你说什么
What'd you say?
不管你有多么想自杀
No matter how bad you want to,
不管你要尝试多少种方法
No matter how many different ways you try,
你是不会成功的
It won happen.
如果你不相信我  你可以开枪试试
Give it a shot if you don't belie me.
你有更重要的事要做  Mike
You got more work to do, mike.
如果你想通了
When you figure that out,
到Earle酒店的顶楼来找我
I'm in the penthouse at the hotel earle.
大洋航空815航班的残骸
The wreckage of oceanic flight 815
已经找到
Has them found.
这组连续镜头确定了
This footage confirms
飞机的确失事并沉入海底
The airplane did, in fact, crash at sea.
在这么深的海洋中
At these tremendous depths,
找到幸存者的希望几乎为零
There is little hope of recovering any remains.
调查人员也在怀疑
Investigators are equally skeptical
是否能找到大洋航空815航班的
About the chances of retrieving
黑匣子
Oceanic 815's black box.
这架不幸的飞机
The real story behind
到底发生了什么  其真相
What happened to this fateful airliner
也许就会像机上324名乘客一样  再也找不回来
May have been lost along with the 324 passengers onboard.
但是即使是这个悲惨的发现
But even with this tragic discovery,
遇难者家属今天仍希望...
The victims' families were hoping today...
我没想到你会这么快
I didn't expect you that fast.
这就是拿香槟瓶砸你头的家伙
Is this the guy who hit you with the champagne bottle?
没错  不过我马上就要报这个仇了
Yeah, but I had it coming.
Arturo  我要和Michael谈点事
Arturo, michael and I have some business to attend to.
-你出去透透气吧?  -行
Would you get some air? of course.
再见
Ciao.
要不要吃点
Help yourself to the chow.
这东西在国内可不常吃...
Don't make it to the mainland too often...
所以要是一有机会  我就会狂吃一顿
So when I do, I like to indulge myself.
你们的人都能来去自如?
So you people can just... come and go?
一部分人吧  要喝点什么吗?
Some of us. you want a drink?
我要你告诉我
What I want is for you to tell me
那飞机在海底怎么了
What my plane is doing at the bottom of the ocean.
没有所谓的飞机  那是个幌子
That's not your plane. it's a phony.
有个叫Widmore人把那玩意沉下去的
A man named Widmore put it down there,
伪造所有的残骸
And he staged the whole wreck.
伪造?  他为什么伪造
Staged? why would he stage a--
因为不想让人知道
Because he doesn't want anyone else finding
真正的飞机是在哪失事  除了他自己
Where the real plane ended up... except for him.
你以为我会相信吗?
I'm supposed to believe this?
子弹被你的头盖骨反弹出来了?
Did the bullet bounce off your skull,
还是那枪卡了?
Or did the gun just jam on you?
证明一下
Prove it.
什么?
Sorry?
证明Widmore这家伙  真是如你所言
Prove that this guy, Widmore, did what you say he did.
证明给我啊
Prove it.
那是泰国的公墓
That's the cemetery in Thailand
Widmore从那里挖了300具尸体
Where Widmore dug up the 300-odd corpses he needed.
这是他从一家空壳公司
And the purchase order for the old 777
买了份老的777飞机的定单
Bought through a shell company,
和货船的航海日志
And the shipping logs for the freighter he used
使得事情变得更加扑朔迷离
To drop the whole mess down a trench deep enough
为了确保每个残骸都无法被识别出来
To guarantee that no remains are ever gonna be identified.
你能想象  为了运来这些尸体
Do you have any idea what it would cost
我们付出怎样的代价吗?
To bring those bodies up?
你要我怎么做?
What you want from me, man?
几天后
In a few days,
会有艘货船在斐济停靠
A freighter is porting in fiji.
是Widmore的船
It's widmore's boat.
我们有理由相信他终于在岛上
We have reason to believe he's finally found
找到同党了  他正要向那里去
The coordinates of the island, and he's heading right for it.
那么恭喜你  Michael  你的星际旅行到此为止了
So congratulations, michael. your shore leave is over.
你待在那船上只要做一件事就行
You just got a job on that boat.
去找Kevin Johnson
Meet Kevin Johnson.
你在斐济加入他们  做一名甲板水手
You're joining the crew in fiji as a deckhand.
你要我去卧底?
You want me to go unrcover?
我到底凭什么回那去替你们卖命?
Why the hell would I go back to work for you people?
因为如果Widmore找到了这个岛
Because if widmore finds the island,
那岛上的人都得死
It's good night for everybody on it.
他眼都不眨就会把所有的人杀光殆尽
He'll kill them all without thinking twice.
你要想挽回你的过失?
You wanna redeem yourself for what you did?
这是你唯一的机会
This is your only chance.
你能救他们所有人的命
You can save all their lives.
不  我不行  我不能再回去了
No. I can't. I can't go back to that island.
我又没叫你回岛上去
I didn't say you were going back to the island.
只叫你上那艘船  你可以擦擦甲板  Michael
You're going on that boat so you can swab decks, michael.
这样你就有机会把船上的统统干掉
You're going so you can kill everyone onboard.
嘿 你是工程师?
Hey. You are engineer?
不是
Nah.
只是个甲板水手
Just a deckhand.
在船上  大家都人人平等的
Well, we're all equals on this boat...
只要你规规矩矩的
As long as you play decent hold'em.
我叫George Minkowsk
I'm George... Minkowsk
Kevin Johnson
Kevin johnson.
很高兴见到你  Kevin
Ah, nice to meet you, Kevin.
那好  你去那边Naomi那登记下吧
All right, well, why don't you go check in
呆会见  欢迎啊
With Naomi over there? and, uh I'll be seeing you? welcome.
我来报到的  我是Kevin Johnson
I'm reporting for duty. Kevin Johnson.
Naomi Dorrit  很高兴见到你
Naomi Dorrit. pleasure.
你从美国来的?
So you're from the states, yeah?
-口音能听出来  -你是曼彻斯特人?
Yeah, I could tell from the accent. Manchester?
你怎么知道的?  上船吧
How'd you guess? You can head onboard.
哦  这有个箱子是寄给你的
Oh, uh, one of these crates was delivered for you.
要我叫人送到你船位吗?
I'll have it divered to your berth?
好的  谢谢你
Yeah. thanks.
欢迎上船  Kevin
Welcome aboard, Kevin.
你不是Kevin
Your name isn't Kevin.
别担心
Don't worry.
船上80%的人都心怀鬼胎
80% of the people on this boat are lying about something.
来个桔子吗?
Orange?
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks.
喂?  旅途怎么样?
Yeah? how was your trip?
我猜你对坐飞机不是太感冒
I figure flying can't be too much fun for you.
你要怎么样?
What do you want?
拿到包裹了吗?
You get your care package?
-是的  -再过一两天
Yeah. wait a day or two untill
等船开到远海  你再下手
You're out in the open sea, then you're good to go.
你可以把所有的工具都搬到地下室  知道了吗
You can stow your gear downstairs, all right?
欢迎欢迎  Keamy
Welcome aboard, keamy.
哦  有几个你见过的
Oh, you met some of 'em now.
或是见过他们本人  或是听过他们的名字
Got some names and faces,
-你怕得手脚发冷了吧?  -没错  是的
And you're gettin' cold feet, huh? yeah, actually, I am.
听着  我再给你报几个过去
Listen, here are a few more names for ya--
Sun  Sawyer  Jack
Sun, sawyer, jack,
Claire及她的孩子
Claire, her baby.
你唯一能救他们的办法
And the only way you're gonna save their lives
就是你要振作起来  登上那艘船
Is if you man up and get on that boat.
要不你还可以回来对你的孩子解释
Or maybe you wanna come back and explain to your kid
你是怎么眼睁睁的看着他们死去
How you let all of them die, too.
是时候了  你要加进来还退是出去?
It's game time. are you in or out?
我去
I'm in.
那把你的手机扔了  马上去工作吧
Then ditch your phone and go do your job.
恕我冒犯  不过我开船时
No offense but I was flying these things
你还在上在小学呢
When you were still in grade chool.
-要是得有人去的话  也是我去  -好吧  我要你
If anybody's gotta go first, it should be me. Yeah, I need you get
-把科考队运到就行了  Frank  -你到底要干嘛?
Transport the science team, Frank. what the hell are you gonna be doing?
这不关你的事
That's need-to-know. you don't.
好男不跟女斗
So much for the fairer sex, huh?
我叫Frank Lapidus  直升机驾驶员
Frank Lapidus, chopper pilot.
Kevin Joson
Kevin joson.
甲板水手
Deckhand.
你有什么故事吗  Kevin?
So what's your story, Kevin?
什么?
Sorry?
你怎么沦落到这了?
How'd you end up on this tub?
就是想来次小小的探险
Looking for a little adventure.
啊  探险 没错
Ah, adventure. Yeah.
你喜欢这次探险吗?
Well, how do you like this for adventure?
你没有听过大洋815航班的事故?
You ever hear about oceanic 815?
听过
Yeah.
要是我告诉你
What would you say if I told you
他们在那条海沟里找到的残骸
The plane they found in that trench
不是大洋815航班  你会怎么想呢
Wasn't oceanic 815?
那又会是什么呢?
Then what is it?
你知道有些白痴还怀疑人类登月是造假的?
You know those nuts that think the moon landing was faked?
这么说吧...
Well, this is like that...
真正的事实
Only real.
这就是我为什么要来这的原因
That's why I signed up for this trip,
因为船主信任我
Because the owner of this boat believes me.
Charles Widmore
Charles widmore.
他相信815飞机一定另在别处
He believes that 815 is still out there somewhere.
我是说  你能想象这会有多轰动...
I mean, can you imagine what would happen...
要是我们发现还有幸存者?
If we'd found some of those people alive?
放!
Pull!
再来一盒弹夹  干得不错
Another clip. good job.
放!
Pull!
扣杀  耶
Kill shot! yeah!
你们在嘛呢?
What are you guys doing?
你觉得我们像是在干嘛?
What's it look like we're doing?
我们在射击
We're shooting things
放!
Pull!
我...
I, uh...
以为我们要去营救
Thought we were going on a rescue mission.
难道你清洁工作做完了?
Don't you have something to mop up?
快点  我们继续
Come on. let's go.
放!
Pull!
你可以的  伙计  你能行
You can do this, man. you can do this.
7... 1...
7-7-6
7-7-6.
好了
Okay.
不要按  Michael
Don't do it, michael.
我爱你  Walt
I love you, Walt.
怎么了  你要扮演Nicholson
What, are you going Nicholson on us?
-什么?  -你看过"炫耀"吗
What? you know, Jack Nicholson in "the shining,"
Jack Nicholson对着强掷球
When he's bouncing that ball against the wall?
后来...  你知道
Next thing you know,
你要拿着斧头追你妻子
You're gonna go after your wife with an ax.
我还没结婚  伙计
I'm not married, man.
好吧  抱歉打断你  有你的电话
Well, I'm sorry to interrupt, but you got a call.
电话?
A call?
是的  从陆地上打来的
Yeah. from the mainland.
他们把它转到无线电室
They patched it through to the radio room.
搞错了吧  伙计  没人知道我在这
It's gotta be a mistake, man. nobody even knows I'm here.
但是船上就你叫Kevin Johnson
Well, you're the only Kevin Johnson onboard,
所以肯定有人知道你在这
So somebody knows you're here.
他说他必须和你通话  他叫Walt
Said he really needs to talk to you. his name's Walt.
给  嘿...
Yeah, here you go. hey, uh...
有点私事  我能单独呆着吗
It's kind of personal. mind if I take this alone?
慢慢聊  Kev
Take your time, Kev.
你只需按下这黄色按钮
You just push this yellow button
然后  把这旋钮转到控制台  知道了吗
And, uh, turn this knob on the console. got it.
知道了
Okay.
Walt?
抱歉  Michael  他还在纽约
I'm so sorry, Michael, but he's still in new york.
恐怕你只能和我混了
So I'm afraid you're stuck with me.
Michael
Michael?
还在听吗
Are you still there?
你把我骗到这船上
You put me on this boat,
叫我把这船炸掉
Talked me into blowing it up,
当我按下该死的按钮
And when I push the damn button,
却出现了一张纸条
A flag pops up.
你真的激活了炸弹吗
You actually activated the bomb?
根本就不是什么炸弹!  是个...
It's not a bomb! it's a...
只是个玩笑
It's a joke.
船上有些人是无辜的
There are people on your boat who are innocent.
他们毫不知情
They have no idea
不知道他们的雇主是个恶魔
That the man they work for is a monster,
没有良知的杀人犯不会有更大的作为
A killer without conscience wouldn't get a greater purpose.
我得让你知道我和他是不一样
I had to show you the difference between him and me.
在战争时期  我会不折手段去赢得胜利
When I'm at war, I'll do what I need to do to win,
但是我不会杀死无辜百姓
But I will not kill innocent people.
Ana Lucia和Libby...
Ana Lucia and Libby...
她们也是无辜的啊
They were innocent.
是你杀死了他们  Michael
You killed them, Michael.
没人叫你这么干
No one asked you to.
我这不是在怪你  Michael
I don't blame you, Michael.
你儿子确实在我们手上
We did you have your boy.
一个男人为他儿子有什么不会做的呢?
And what wouldn'a man do for his son?
你想要我...做什么?
What do you want... from me?
我要你给我一份名单
I want you to compile a list of names...
要船上所有人的名字
Every person on your boat.
当我再次打电话来  你就得告诉我
When I call again, you'll give me that list.
然后你就废了
Then you will disable
你所在通讯室
The radio room you're sitting in.
当他们因无法通讯而迷航时
When the crew is disiented by their lack of communication,
你就把出发动机也卸了
You'll take out the engines, too.
这样  这船就永远都到不了这个岛
That way, the boat can never get to this island,
你的朋友也会安然无恙
And your friends will be safe.
你能做到吗  Michael
Will you do that for me, Michael?
能
Yeah.
那么你就继续装作和他们一伙的吧
Then consider yourself one of the good guys.
你是说...
So you're telling me...
你在为Benjamin Linus卖命
That you're working for Benjamin Linus?
是的
Yeah.
是的  我就是这意思
Yeah, that's what I'm telling you.
放手
Hold it! uhh!
放开我  你要嘛?
Let me go! what are you doing?!
闭嘴!
Shut your mouth
这是怎么回事?
What the hell is this?
这人不是你想象的那样简单
This man is not who you think he is.
他是大洋815航班的乘客
He was a passenger onceanic flight 8-1-5.
在出卖我们之前
I spent two months with him on the island
我们一起在岛上呆了两个月
Before he betrayed us.
就是他捣毁了你们的通讯室
This is the man who sabotaged your radio room.
他把船的发动机也毁了
He destroyed the ship's engine,
他也不叫Ken Johnson
And his name isn't Ken Johnson.
他是Michael Dawson
It's michael dawson,
他是叛徒
And he's a traitor.
停下来喝点水吧
Stop here and drink.
两分钟后我们继续赶路
Two minutes, then we keep moving.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
Karl
Karl.
我也不清楚
I don't know.
只是有种不详的预感
I just he a bad feeling about this.
要是你父亲...在玩弄我们怎么办?
What if your dad is... playing us?
听着  我不想接受他的命令
Look, I don't like taking orders from my dad
比你还不想
Any more than you do.
但我知道他不会让我受到伤害的
But I know he doesn' want me to get hurt.
好吧  至少我们又有共同点了
Well, at least we've got something in common.
你得保证不要和别人说
Promise not to tell if you won't.
-Alex!   -Karl!
Alex! karl!
-Karl  Karl  不要  -快点
Karl, karl! no! come on.
-不要  -快走  他已经死了
No! no! co on! he's gone.
Alex!
不要!
No!
-我们必须带上Karl  -Karl已经死了  他死了!
No, no, we have to get karl. karl! s gone. he's gone!
-不!  -他死了  听我说  我要你抓住我的手
No. he gone! listen to me. I need you to take my hand.
我数一二三  我们就跑
On the count of three, we're going to run.
你能做到吗?
Can you do that with me?
我爱你
I love you.
我非常爱你  Alexana
I love you very much, Alexana.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
一...
One...
二...
Two...
三!
Three!
等等!  等等!  我是Ben的女儿
Wait! Wait! don' I'm Ben's daughter!
我是他女儿!
I'm his daughter!
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示 |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国) 双语字幕校正 时间轴调整
英语翻译 欧美影视新闻翻译 影视评论 论坛版主 美工人员
服务器提供者 发布宣传 联系地址：www.YYeTs.net
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====